# Nguyen Bui Duy Phong - Full Stack Software Engineer Phone: +84 947443064 / Email: phchmessibar326@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> / <u>GitHub</u>

#### SUMMARY

I'm a Full Stack Software Engineer with more 2 years of experience in Web Development and Mobile Development. I have 3 years of experience working with JavaScript/TypeScript and Node-related Frameworks/Platforms.

With my knowledge of backend/frontend development requirements and UI/UX design, I enjoy solving technical problems and creating quality apps for users. I also spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better engineer.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript & TypeScript

# Frameworks / Platforms:

- · ReactJS, NextJS, React Native
- MaterialUI, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Konva, Rneui,...
- · NodeJS ExpressJS, NestJS, Keycloak, Swagger
- Webpack/Babel, Web API

**Database Management Systems:** Mongo DB, Mongo Atlas, Mongo Compass **Cloud Management Systems:** AWS S3, Heroku, Netlify, Vercel, Digital Ocean

**CI/CD:** Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins **Foreign Languages:** Basic English

Other Tools: Github, GitLab, Jira, Bitbucket, Figma, Zeplin,...

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# DigiEx Group (Viet Nam) - Full Stack Software Engineer

03/2022 - Now

Project: Obello (18 members, 6 front-end, 3 back-end, other positions)

01/2023 - Now

- **Description:** A graphic design application that helps users to quickly create intelligent Template Designs by providing images, videos, graphics and fonts around the client's brand by integrating artificial intelligence
- Position: Front-end Developer
- · Technologies:
  - Microservices architecture setup with Webpack in Front-end
  - Core Front-end: JavaScript, ReactJS, Mobx, MUIv6, Konva, react-spring
  - Back-end: Java, NodeJS, MongoDB, AWS

# · Responsibilities:

- Define the architecture, global stores management for Editor platform service. Working on Animation Module, apply the animation for the element in template, connect and run animations between templates of a project to extract into video previews and adjust Editor platform behaviors related to animation
- Setup and define the structure for Guidelines service. Handle Video/Illustration/Color/Deleted Module
  of Brand's element management service
- Host daily meeting with Dev team, cross code review in the team to ensure code quality
- Investigate solutions with Technical Architect for important sections, create the roadmap for specify
   Module & giving estimation to the item on the product roadmap

Project: Kokozi (5 members) - Full-stack Leader Developer

10/2022 - 1/2023

 Description: Built a gateway with multiple authentication, authorization methods (OAuth 2.0, OpenID Connect, JWT, SMS) use with affiliate partners in the client's system

#### · Technologies:

- Front-end: ReactJS, React Native, Web View, Apple/Kakao/Firebase/Typeform Sdk
- Back-end: NestJS, Keycloak

## · Responsibilities:

- Legacy the authentication's interface on the web application, extends the cross-platform application with React Native, uses Web View to load and run the code on the native environment
- Setup Keycloak Admin Console's interface to help client manage users effectively, integrate Apple/Kakao service into Keycloak's system to categorize user channels
- Implement protocol's flows, integrating the APIs provided by Keycloak to create APIs for use by the system and third parties
- Assign tasks, support and transfer task to Junior members & report daily with client

# Project: Calobye (9 members) - Front-end Developer

7/2022 - 10/2022

• **Description:** Develop an SEO optimized e-commerce website including sales channels and store management channels

## · Technologies:

Front-end: NextJS + ReactJS, Typescript, MUIv6

Back-end: Java, MySQL

#### · Responsibilities:

- Participate in the early stages of the project, setup modules according to the old design of the project
- Mainly coding and fixing bugs, implement module Home page & Product page

Project: CafeMaker (3 members) - Front-end Developer

07/2022

• Technologies: React Native, React-native-chart

Project: ITruck (3 members) - Front-end Developer

03/2022 - 06/2022

• Technologies: React Native, Redux, Rneui

# Other projects

Project: VietCredit (7 members) - Full-stack Developer

• Technologies: Node, Express, MongoDB, React, Flutter, Web view

# **EDUCATION**

Majored in Information Technology at Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education (HCMUTE) 2019-2023